(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-31T16:56:36.645147",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あくあ色すーぱーみらくるどりーむ♪
[Aqua-iro Super Miracle Dream♪]
YouTube Live 開催決定！
[YouTube Live Confirmed!]
2021.05.09 21:00〜
[May 9, 2021, 21:00~]
メイドの日（5月10日）を記念した3Dライブ！
[A 3D Live Commemorating Maid Day (May 10)!]
ご主人様への感謝を込めて
[With Gratitude to Our Masters]
ガチ歌ライブをYouTubeでお届け！
[Bringing You a Serious Singing Live on YouTube!]
あくあ色すーぱーみらくるどりーむ♪
[Aqua-iro Super Miracle Dream♪]
お帰りなさい、ご主人様
Welcome home, Master.
AQUA Ch. 100万人達成！
[AQUA Ch. Reached 1 Million Subscribers!]
メイドの日（5月10日）
[Maid Day (May 10)]
記念3D LIVE!!
[Commemorative 3D LIVE!!]
湊あくあ
[Minato Aqua]
手紙が届きましたよ
A letter has arrived for you.
love you love you love you love you 信じてねーねー
Love you, love you, love you, love you, believe in me...
大丈夫 あくあ色に染めるよ
It's okay, I'll dye you in Aqua color.
キミと歩く この未来を
Walking towards this future with you.
いつも隣にいるし
I'm always by your side,
いつも一緒に笑える 私をたくさん知って たくさん好きって言って
Always laughing together, get to know me more and tell me you love me lots!
ワガママで朝も苦手 ドジだしダメダメだけど それでも私のこと見ててね
Selfish, bad mornings, clumsy and hopeless, but still, look at me!
描く夢の未来へ続く
Leading to the future of dreams we draw,
道をキミと歩けますように
May I walk this path with you.
ねえ もっと! 好きになってもらいたいのに 頭の中は君ばっか!!
Hey, more! I want you to love me more! My head is full of just you!!
って言うかそっそうなんても向いてないで! あぁもう! ヤキモキしちゃうわ あぁ
I mean, don't look away like that! Ah geez! It makes me so impatient, ah!
ずーずーっと好きがいいの 心の奥もときめいちゃうくらいに こっち向いてよねだーりん?
I want you to love me forever and ever, enough to make my heart flutter deep inside, won't you look this way, darling?
あぁもう離さないから、絶対に!
Ah geez, I'm never letting go, absolutely!
love you love you love you love you love you love you aishite motto
Love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love me more!
伝えるのは下手だから 勘違いしないで聞いてよね
I'm bad at conveying my feelings, so listen without misunderstanding, okay?
私なりの応援だから 分かるでしょう ねぇ笑ったって泣いたって
It's my own way of cheering you on, so you understand, right? Whether crying or laughing,
一度に言って頑張って頑張って ここに来た 君がいなきゃ絶対
Tell me all at once, "Do your best!" If you weren't here, I'd definitely
たどり着けなかった場所だから
Never have reached this place.
love you love you love you love you
今度はぎゅっと私から
This time, I will hold you tight
キミの背中をお手強く優しくね
And gently, strongly support your back!
love you love you love you love you 前を向いて最後は
Love you, love you, love you, love you, look forward, and finally,
見たこともない世界 一緒に旅しようよ
Let's journey together to a world we've never seen before!
みんな!きゅきゅっとみりしてくれてありがとう!
Everyone! Thank you so much for watching me closely!
近代チャイルドなみなったんが
Minattan, who is a modern child,
いっぱい歌うから みんなたくさんコメントしてね!
Will sing a lot, so everyone, leave lots of comments!
よかったら え・き・ゅ・ゆ・え のところでコメントで え・き・ゅ・ゆ・え
If you'd like, at "A-Q-U-A", comment "A-Q-U-A"
あくあしか勝たんって言ってね!
And say "Aqua is the best!"
負けたくない悔しさや涙があふれた日日すらも無駄じゃない私らしさを作っていく
Even the days overflowing with frustration and tears of not wanting to lose are not wasted; they make me who I am.
だから大丈夫大丈夫心配ないよ大丈夫大丈夫全力で走り続けたんだ
So it's okay, it's okay, no need to worry, it's okay, it's okay, I ran with all my might.
キミならできるさ
You can do it!
喜びも悲しみも分かち合えるひとがいる初めて気づいたんだ一人じゃないんだって
I realized for the first time that there is someone to share joy and sadness with, that I am not alone.
love you love you love you love you なったまたちと叶えたい夢はきっとこの場所で
Love you, love you, love you, love you, the dream I want to fulfill with everyone is surely right here,
あくあ色に輝く
Shining in Aqua color!
え・き・ゅ・ゆ・え 行くよLet's go!
A-Q-U-A, here we go, Let's go!
あ・い・う・え・お・あくあ・for the win!
A-I-U-E-O Aqua for the win!
love you love you love you love you あくあ for the win ありがとう!
Love you, love you, love you, love you, Aqua for the win, thank you!
振らめいて 綺羅めいて
Oh my, oh my, oh, my love, is truly galactic...
それでも心は ひ・み・つ だから
Still, my heart is a s-e-c-r-e-t, after all.
なぜだか胸が高鳴るの (キュン)
No idea why, but my heart goes haywire (thump-thump!)
あなたと言葉交わすたび (ピッと)
Whenever I exchange words with you. (beep!)
以心伝心異次元の精度で
It's telepathy from a different world.
思考リーディング
Thinking reading!
アタマに生えた触覚に (キュン)
The antennae that sprang from your head (thump-thump!)
それがオシャレと言うけれど (ピッと)
Were super stylish and all, but (beep!)
わたし見たのよ 光るとこ
I definitely saw it! They were glowing!
気になって 眠れない
I'm so curious I can't sleep!
知らないうちに恋してる
A heart that falls in love in the blink of an eye
ハートと似てるね
suits me, doesn't it?
あなたの事ばかりを 考えちゃってさ
All I end up thinking about is you.
振らめいて (イェーイ!) 綺羅めいて (イェーイ!)
Oh my, (yeah!) oh my, (yeah!) oh, my love,
それでも心は ひ・み・つ
is truly galactic.
UFO UFO ユウフォウが
It wavers, it sparkles too...
迎えにきても平気だよ
Still, my heart is a s-e-c-r-e-t.
「知りたいな」 (イェーイ!) 言えないな... (イェーイ!)
Even if a UFO came to pick me up, that'd be a-o-k!
あなたの全ては ひ・み・つ
I can't manage to ask, "Tell me about yourself."
ピーポーピーポー おかしな気持ち
Everything about you is a s-e-c-r-e-t.
ピーポーピーポー 不思議な言葉を
Wee-woo, wee-woo, funny little you,
ピーポーピーポー 交わしましょう ピピピ
wee-woo, wee-woo, and my funny little feelings.
昨日の放送の映画でも (キュン)
In the movie that aired yesterday too, (thump-thump!)
あなたによく似た生命体 (ピッと)
There were lifeforms that looked a lot like you. (beep!)
その姿のイメージは (キュン)
The image of their appearance...
勝手な想像だけれど
might've just been my skewed bias.
信じているよ 恋してるハートよりも強く
I still believe I'm stronger than my love-ridden heart,
あなたの事ばかりで やんなっちゃうな
but all I think about is you. Aaah, this sucks!
押したって 引いたって
Pushing forward, pulling away...
ダメダメ心は ひ・み・つ
No, I can't! My heart's a s-e-c-r-e-t.
ほんとは大好きさ ギャラクティック
Oh my, oh my, oh, my love –
秘密はまだまだ ひ・み・つ
the one I truly love is galactic.
UFO UFO ユウフォウで 迎えにきてよ 今すぐ!
They're fickle and fluttering.
勘違いって (イェーイ!) 間違って (イェーイ!)
The secret's still a s-e-c-r-e-t.
いても恋したの ひ・み・つ
Please pick me up in the UFO! I can't wait any longer!
ピーポーピーポー おかしな気持ち
There was a misunderstanding, I made a mistake –
ピーポーピーポー 不思議な言葉を
but even so, it was a "s-e-c-r-e-t" I loved.
ピーポーピーポー 交わしましょう ピピピ
Wee-woo, wee-woo, funny little you,
嫌いじゃないとかそんなんじゃない エネルギーあってもできないしょうがないなって許してよ
Wee-woo, wee-woo, and my funny little feelings.
エンジェルリングをオーバーしながらこんな私に誰がしたなんてこんな私に私でしたのがしょうがないなって許してよ
Wee-woo, wee-woo, let's have a dialogue
エンジェルリングをオーバーしながら天使の翼は使ってない 飛ぶの怖いから
wee-woo, wee-woo, of strange words. Beep-beep-beep.
本気を出したら飛べますか? みたいな顔をしている
Even if a UFO came to pick me up, that'd be a-o-k!
そんなハリボテの裏側に 隠した愛の感情が
I can't manage to ask, "Tell me about yourself."
あなたに笑ってほしいの
Everything about you is a s-e-c-r-e-t.
ねえ ダメ ダメ ダメ ダメな私で
Wee-woo, wee-woo, funny little you,
いいですか?
wee-woo, wee-woo, and my funny little feelings.
実際は一切の自信もないような
Wee-woo, wee-woo, let's have a dialogue
天使ですが
wee-woo, wee-woo, of strange words. Beep-beep-beep.
クルクルクルクルと巡る 頭の中では
In the movie that aired yesterday too, (thump-thump!)
あなたのことばかり
There were lifeforms that looked a lot like you. (beep!)
考えてるんだ
The image of their appearance...
ダメ ダメ ダメ ダメな私を
might've just been my skewed bias.
愛してよ もらった愛とボトムのようよ
I still believe I'm stronger than my love-ridden heart,
天使だから ドキドキドキドキをあげるよ
but all I think about is you. Aaah, this sucks!
あなたには もっと好きになってくれるなら
Pushing forward, pulling away...
やるよ多分 ドキドキドキドキ天使は
No, I can't! My heart's a s-e-c-r-e-t.
ドキドキドキドキでしょ?
Oh my, oh my, oh, my love –
だけど私はいいか? やんないじゃないできないんだとや?
the one I truly love is galactic.
や、でも届くわしますとや?
They're fickle and fluttering.
改めてまして 皆さんどうもこんあくあー!
Thank you all so much for coming!
みなとあくあですー!
Minato Aqua here!
いやね 早速 飛ばして行いきましたが
Well, we quickly flew right through it,
みんな ついてこれてるー? イエーイ!
but you all made it here! Yay!
大丈夫かなー?
Are you doing okay?
今日ね この3Dライブ
Today's 3D live...
えー ま 企画したのは 1月に え YouTubeチャンネル登録者数が
Back in January, thanks to you all,
ありがたいことに 100万人を突破いたしまして
we surpassed 1 million subscribers,
そちらの え ま 記念というか ね
so we're holding this commemorative stream.
えーと ま 配信 記念配信 っていう感じで え やらさせていただきました! アリガトネ みんな! ありがとうございまーす!
Thank you so much, everyone! Thank you!
いや もう あっという間にもう5月になっちゃったけども
And just like that, it's already May!
ま でもおね こう 歌に ダンスに
But you know, with the singing, the dancing,
それにね なんか いっぱいね こう セットとかもね すっごいね いい感じになっててね
and all these sets, it turned out really nice,
すごいね こう 力をも 蓄えてきたので
and I've been building up so much energy!
よかったら最後まで楽しんでってもらえたらいいなって思ってるよ!
I hope you'll enjoy it all the way to the end.
よろしくね また待ってくれてありがとね! ありがとう!
See you soon! Thanks for waiting!
というわけで ま ね みなとあくあ おさいきん知ったよって人ね いてくれてると思うんだけれども
So, some of you might know, back in August last year
ま 去年 開催した あくあ色すーぱーどりーむ っていう8月に行った ソロライブがあるんだけれども
we held "AQUA IRO SUPER DREAM."
ま 今回 あくあ色すーぱーみらくるどりーむ ということで
Well, this time it's "AQUA IRO SUPER MIRACLE DREAM,"
見てほしい 全部見てほしいけど 見てみな感じのね ちょっとショートバージョンで
I want you to watch. I want you to watch it all, but in a sort of short version...
今回は、え、YouTubeのみんなにお届けできたらいいなって思ってますー。
...this time, we hope to deliver it to everyone on YouTube!
まあワンマンライブにね、参加してくれたみんなもね、あ、見なくていいじゃんってなんないように
Also, for everyone who participated in the solo live, so you don't feel like "oh, I don't need to watch this,"
新曲を用意して
we've prepared a new song,
おろしますので、頑張って覚えてきたから、よかったら最後まで見てね！よろしくー！
so since I worked hard to memorize it, I hope you'll watch till the end! Thanks!
ということで、あ、みんなね、コメントねいっぱいしてくれてありがとね。
And so, oh, thank you everyone for leaving so many comments.
じゃあね、あっ、ちょっとね、あの歌とかね、ちょっと歌うから、あんまり読むことはできないんですけれど
Well, um, since I'll be singing a bit, I won't be able to read them much, but
ちゃんと見てます！ありがとー！ありがとねー！
I'm watching properly! Thank you! Thank you!
ということで、あ、そうだ！この後ね、このライブの後の話になっちゃうんだけど
And so, oh right! After this, it'll be about after this live, but
ライブの後、え、メンバー限定生放送で、えっと3Dでちょっとね、あの話したり、ちょっとこのねライブの後の感想会したり
after the live, um, in the member-limited stream, in 3D, we'll talk a bit, do an after-party/impressions chat about this live,
えっと写真を撮ったりするのね、よかったらねメンバーに、え、なってくれた人たちはね一緒に見ましょう。ぜひなってない人は今からなろう。よろしく頼む！
and take photos. If you're a member, let's watch together! If you aren't yet, become one now. Please look forward to it!
今日なんか動きおかしいね。やばい、緊張してんのかも。
Today my movements feel a bit weird. Oh no, maybe I'm nervous.
はい、ということで、えー、それではね、長々と話してしまいましたが、次の曲いきたいと思います！
Right, so, um, well I've talked for quite a long time, but let's move on to the next song!
その前に、いしゃー、ちぇーんじ！
Before that... switch!
ということで、次の曲聞いてください。気まぐれロマンティック！
And with that, please listen to the next song. Kimagure Romantic!
ロマンティック 恋のアンテナは 嵐で何処へ飛んでいっていた
Romantic, my love's antenna got blown away by a storm
嘘でしょう 冷たくあしらった こしゃくなエクボに ちょっと 心が揺れている
That can't be, I treated you coldly, but my heart is shaking at your cheeky dimples
ホントは 本気で私を 叱ってくれる大事なひと
Actually, you're an important person who sincerely scolds me
…なんて言ったらアイツは 得意気になるから もう褒めたりしないけど
...but if I told you that, you'd act all smug, so I won't praise you anymore
退屈な運命に 飽き飽きしたの 知らない台詞で解きほぐしてね
I'm sick and tired of this boring destiny. Untangle me with unfamiliar words, okay?
ダーリン ダーリン 心の扉を 壊してよ
Darling, darling, break down the door to my heart
大切なことは 瞳を見て 曇って
Look into my eyes and tell me what's important
あなたとならば この街を抜け出せる
If I'm with you, I can sneak out of this town
今すぐ 連れ出して My Sweet Sweet Darling
Take me away right now, My Sweet Sweet Darling
ドラマティック 笑顔の秘密を だれだって探し続けてる
Dramatic, everyone keeps searching for the secret of a smiling face
見上げた 空に描くの 幸せのかち… そう あたらしいいたい
I'll draw happiness in the sky above, yes, I want to be true to myself
気まぐれなテンションで 振りまわすけど
I'll spin you round and round with bold tension
この手は必ず 離さないで ね
But remember not to let go of my hand, okay?
ダーリン ダーリン 心の扉を 叩いてよ
Darling, darling, knock on the door to my heart
素直な気持ちが あふれていく
I can feel my honest emotions welling up inside
あなたとならば 笑っていられるよ
I can see myself laughing together with you
今すぐ 駆け出すの My Sweet Sweet Darling
We're taking off right now, My Sweet Sweet Darling
ダーリン ダーリン きっと 私をつかめるよ
Darling, darling, I know you can capture me
幸せの意味に 気づいていく
I'm realizing what happiness is
あなたとならば 明日を変えられる
I'm seeing a new tomorrow together with you
今すぐ 連れ出して My Sweet Sweet Darling
Take me away now, My Sweet Sweet Darling
ロマンティック 恋のアンテナは
Romantic, my love’s antenna
嵐で何処かへ飛んでいった
got blown away by a storm.
嘘でしょう 冷たくあしらった
That can’t be, I treated him like ice.
こしゃくなエボクに ちょっと 心が揺れてる
My heart is shaking at his brazenness.
ホントは 本気であなたを
Actually, when he gets all serious
説教してくれる大事なひと
and scolds me, he's someone important...
…なんて言ったらアイツは
But if I said that, he'd get so proud,
得意気にするから
so no more compliments from me.
もう褒めたりしない
I'm tired of this boring destiny.
タイクツな運命に飽き飽きしたの
Free me with words I've never heard before!
知らない台詞で 解き放して ね
Free me with words I've never heard before, okay?
ダーリン ダーリン
Darling, darling,
心の扉を 壊してよ
break down the door to my heart!
たいせつなことは
You need to look into my eyes
瞳を見て 雲って
and tell me that important thing.
あなたとならば
If it's with you,
この街を抜け出せる
I can leave this city behind.
今すぐ 連れ出して
Take me away right now,
My Sweet Sweet Darling
せーのっ
One, two!
でも そんなんじゃだめ
But that's just no good,
もう そんなんじゃほら
no, that's still not right.
心は進化するよ もっともっと
My heart is evolving more and more!
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If words can make our bond disappear,
言葉を消せばいいやって
I thought we could just erase the words.
思ってた 恐れてた だけど あれ?
I was so scared... but wait, why?
なんかちがうかも..
Maybe something's different...
千里の道も一歩から!
Every journey starts with a single step!
石のようにかたい そんな意志で
With a resolve as hard as stone,
ちりも積もれば山となでしこ?
little by little we grow!
「し」抜きで
With all our might—
いや死ぬ気で!
no, like our lives depend on it!
ふわふわり ふわふわり
Floating lightly, floating softly,
あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
just hearing you call my name makes me float on air.
ふわふわり ふわふわり
Floating softly, floating lightly,
あなたが笑っている それだけで笑顔になる
seeing you smile just makes me smile too.
神様ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God, even for fate's little trick,
巡り逢えたことが 幸せなの
being able to meet you is pure happiness.
でも そんなんじゃだめ もう そんなんじゃほら
But that's just no good, no, that's still not right,
心は進化するよ もっともっと
my heart is evolving more and more!
そう そんなんじゃやだ ねぇ そんなんじゃまだ
Yes, that's no good, hey, it's still not enough,
私のこと見ててね ずっとずっと
please keep watching me forever and ever!
でも そんなんじゃだめ
But that's just no good,
もう そんなんじゃほら
no, that's still not right.
心は進化するよ もっともっと
My heart is evolving more and more!
そう そんなんじゃやだ ねぇ そんなんじゃまだ
Yes, that's no good, hey, it's still not enough,
私のこと見ててね ずっとずっと
please keep watching me forever and ever!
私の中のあなたほど あなたの中の私の存在は
Compared to how much you mean to me, my presence in your heart
まだまだ大きくないことも わかってるけれど
is still quite small, I know that very well.
今この同じ瞬間 共有してる 実感
But right now, the feeling of sharing this exact moment
略して?ちりもつもればやまなでしこ!
little by little adds up!
くらくらり くらくらる
Dizzily spinning, spinning round and round,
あなたを見上げたら それだけで眩しすぎて
just looking up at you is so dazzling it blinds me.
くらくらる くらくらり
Spinning round and round, dizzily spinning,
あなたを想っている それだけで溶けてしまう
just thinking about you makes me melt away.
神様ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God, even for fate's little trick,
巡り逢えたことが 幸せなの
being able to meet you is pure happiness.
恋する 季節は 欲張りサーキュレーション
The season of love is a greedy circulation!
恋する 瞳は 欲張りサーキュレーション
Eyes in love are a greedy circulation!
恋する 乙女は 欲張りサーキュレーション
Maidens in love are a greedy circulation!
恋する 季節は 欲張りサーキュレーション
The season of love is a greedy circulation!
ふわふわり ふわふわり あなたが名前を呼ぶ
Floating lightly, floating softly, you call my name,
それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
and that alone makes me float on air.
ふわふわり ふわふわり あなたが笑っている
Floating softly, floating lightly, you are smiling,
それだけで笑顔になる
and that alone makes me smile too.
神様ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God, even for fate's little trick,
巡り逢えたことが 幸せなの
being able to meet you is pure happiness.
でも そんなんじゃだめ もう そんなんじゃほら
But that's just no good, no, that's still not right,
心は進化するよ もっともっと
my heart is evolving more and more!
そう そんなんじゃやだ ねぇ そんなんじゃまだ
Yes, that's no good, hey, it's still not enough,
私のこと見ててね ずっとずっと
please keep watching me forever and ever!
君に Baby Sweet Berry Love
Baby Sweet Berry Love for you,
ホントノキモチだけ 分け合えたらいいのにな
If we could just share our true feelings,
願いを叶えてよ
Make my wish come true!
C.U.T.E. ファニキャット give me give me shiny time P.R.E.T.T.y ティニーティニーベリーラヴ
(C.U.T.E. funny cat give me give me shiny time P.R.E.T.T.y tiny tiny berry love)
大好き！のハートも ゴメンね。のナミダも
Whether it's a heart full of love, or tears of sorriness,
ホントは 素直に見せたくて
I really want you to honestly see.
伝えたい思いと 裏返しの態度 上手に慣れない ココロ模様
Thoughts that I want to say, and an attitude that's different on the inside, I can never make them fit together.
どうして カラマワリ 胸が キュッと なる
Why do things that I did in vain make my heart tighten?
近い 距離 が もどかしい よ ねぇ 届け たい の
The short distance between us is frustrating, oh, I really want to tell you.
君と Baby Sweet Berry Love
Baby Sweet Berry Love with you,
きっと ぎこちなくて でもね 真っ直ぐに見つめて
I know I'm very clumsy, but I still want to keep looking at you,
ソライロ 映したい
Reflecting the colors of the sky.
もっと Baby Sweet Berry Love
Even more Baby Sweet Berry Love,
せめて 君 の 前 で は 笑って 怒って あふれた ありのままでいたい
At least you're still here in front of me, overflowing with happiness and anger, let me show it all to you.
だから Baby Sweet Berry Love
So Baby Sweet Berry Love,
一緒に 始めよう
Let's start now.
C.U.T.E. ファニキャット give me give me shiny time P.R.E.T.T.y ティニーティニーベリーラヴ
(C.U.T.E. funny cat give me give me shiny time P.R.E.T.T.y tiny tiny berry love)
かじられた ハートを 探してみるけれど
Even with a hurt heart I still want to keep searching.
ホント は 自分 の 奥にある
It was deep inside all along.
まるで 寂しいのに すました 迷い猫 こぼれた 夕日 に 嫉妬しちゃう
I thought I was lonely, like a lost stray cat, envious of the sunset.
ふいな 優しさに はしゃぐ 胸の音
Your sudden tenderness is like the sound of heartbeats.
ドタバタ とか カラフル で キュン と 満ちて いく の
Loudly and colorfully filling up inside me.
君と Baby Sweet Berry Love
Baby Sweet Berry Love with you,
なんか 矛盾だらけ 大事であればあるほど
Always full of contradictions, the more important things get,
ごまかしてしまうの
The longer they get stalled.
だけど Baby Sweet Berry Love
But Baby Sweet Berry Love,
自分 の ココロ まで わからない とき は 君 と
I can finally feel my mind whenever I'm not understanding you,
確かめ 合い たい の
Then we'll figure it out together.
だから Baby Sweet Berry Love
So Baby Sweet Berry Love,
同じ 場所 に い たい
I want to be in the same place as you.
君 に Baby Sweet Berry Love 自分 を 守る より 大切な コト が ある の こんなにも 近くに
Baby Sweet Berry Love for you, I want to protect myself, all the important things are in a place this close to me.
君と Baby Sweet Berry Love
Baby Sweet Berry Love with you,
きっと ぎこちなくて でもね 真っ直ぐに見つめて
I know I'm very clumsy, but I still want to keep looking at you,
ソライロ 映したい
Reflecting the colors of the sky.
もっと Baby Sweet Berry Love
Even more Baby Sweet Berry Love,
せめて 君 の 前 で は 笑って 怒って あふれた ありのままでいたい
At least you're still here in front of me, overflowing with happiness and anger, let me show it all to you.
だから Baby Sweet Berry Love
So Baby Sweet Berry Love,
こんなにも スキ だ よ
I love you as much like this.
C.U.T.E. ファニキャット give me give me shiny time P.R.E.T.T.y ティニーティニーベリーラヴ
(C.U.T.E. funny cat give me give me shiny time P.R.E.T.T.y tiny tiny berry love)
ずっと Baby Sweet Berry Love
Always will be Baby Sweet Berry Love.
わからない とき は 君 と
Whenever I'm not understanding you,
確かめ 合い たい の
Then we'll figure it out together.
だから Baby Sweet Berry Love
So Baby Sweet Berry Love,
同じ 場所 に い たい
I want to be in the same place as you.
C.U.T.E. ファニキャット give me give me shiny time P.R.E.T.T.y ティニーティニーベリーラヴ
(C.U.T.E. funny cat give me give me shiny time P.R.E.T.T.y tiny tiny berry love)
君に Baby Sweet Berry Love
Baby Sweet Berry Love for you,
自分 を 守る より 大切な コト が ある の
I want to protect myself, all the important things
こんなにも 近くに
Are in a place this close to me.
君と Baby Sweet Berry Love
Baby Sweet Berry Love with you,
きっと ぎこちなくて でもね 真っ直ぐに見つめて
I know I'm very clumsy, but I still want to keep looking at you,
ソライロ 映したい
Reflecting the colors of the sky.
もっと Baby Sweet Berry Love
Even more Baby Sweet Berry Love,
せめて 君 の 前 で は 笑って 怒って あふれた ありのままでいたい
At least you're still here in front of me, overflowing with happiness and anger, let me show it all to you.
だから Baby Sweet Berry Love
So Baby Sweet Berry Love,
こんなにも スキ だ よ
I love you as much like this.
C.U.T.E. ファニキャット give me give me shiny time P.R.E.T.T.y ティニーティニーベリーラヴ
(C.U.T.E. funny cat give me give me shiny time P.R.E.T.T.y tiny tiny berry love)
ずっと Baby Sweet Berry Love
Always will be Baby Sweet Berry Love.
はーい！ということで、
Hii! So,
ここまで駆け抜けてお届けしていますが、
we've been running and rushing all the way through here,
えー、みんなね、ついこれてますかー？
Um, everyone, are you keeping up?
ついこれてる？みんなー？
Are you keeping up? Everyone?
やっほー、見えてるー？
Yahoo, can you see me?
よいしょ、よいしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho.
あ、
Ah,
これ、これはあの、素直な人にしか見えない、あの水です。飲めます。
This, this is, um, water that can only be seen by honest people. You can drink it.
回復した！
I've recovered!
まぁこういうのもね、ありということでね、いいの、いいの、いいのよ。
Well, things like this are fine too,
it's totally fine!
ということで、もうね、なんと後半に入っている、そうなんだけれども、
So, we've already entered the second half, believe it or not!
なんかさ、さっき誰か来てなかった？え、いたよね？ なんか急にさ、なんか邪魔しに来てた気がするんだけど。
Wait, wasn't someone just here? I feel like someone suddenly came to interrupt.
え、あれ誰だろうね？
I wonder who that was?
え、てかみんな分かった？いま？わかった？ちょっと呼んでみる？
Wait, did you all get it? Just now? Should I call them out?
みんなの、あいつの名前、ちょっと覚えてる？
Does everyone remember that guy's name?
じゃ、いくよ？呼ぶよ？
Alright, here we go! Should I call them?
せーの、ねこー！
Ready, set... Neko!
ねこー！
Neko!
N-E-K-O、ねこー！おっ、来た来た来た来た！ねこ来たー！みんなー！
N-E-K-O, Neko! Oh, they're here! Neko's here! Everyone!
ちょ、ねこ来た！
Hey, Neko's here!
うそでしょ？え？ねこ3D化しちゃったんだけど！
No way? Eh? Neko got made into 3D!
私がものを、なんかね、もうこう「ねこ」と言えばみたいな感じで、ぱーって適当に書いた落書きがですね、なんとここまで3D化してしまいました！
The doodle I casually scribbled thinking "Ah, this is what a cat looks like" got turned into 3D!
やめて、なんかすごい、すごいなんか気持ち悪い動きして、ねえ、やめてよマジ！
Stop it, you're making such creepy movements—seriously, stop it!
気持ち悪いんだよ、動きが。なんか、にょん、にょん、にょん、みたいな動きしてさ。
It's gross, the way it moves. Like squiggly, bouncy movements.
一緒にね、さっき恋愛サーキュレーションもね、踊りましたけれども。
We danced to "Renai Circulation" together just a moment ago, though.
ねえ、かわいいね、めっちゃ。
Man, it's so cute, though.
え、実はね、なんと、ここにみんなにお知らせがありますー！
Oh, actually, I have an announcement for everyone here!
なんとですね、え、ま、このね、え、3Dにもなった猫、え、そして、まね、新衣装でもね、
Believe it or not, this cat that became 3D, and also in my new outfit...
あの次の新衣装でもね、実わね、あの、猫をこうやって抱えて、こうやって抱えて、頭に乗ったりしている、あの猫！
In my next new outfit too, actually, that cat that I hold like this, and put on my head... that cat!
なんとですね、ずっとね、言われてたんだよ。「猫のぬいぐるみ早く出さないの？」って。
People have been telling me forever, "Aren't you releasing a cat plushie soon?"
出ます！なんと！今日！猫ビッグぬいぐるみ公式名称合ってんのかな？わかんない。
It's coming out! Today! The "Big Cat Plush" (wonder if that's the official name).
なんと、作ることになりました、いえーい！
It's officially going to be made, yay!
邪魔してこないで、入ってこないで。入ってくんな、猫！
Don't get in my way, don't come in. Stay out, cat!
やった！やったよ！商品化だよ、猫マジで！あと、出版したね！
We did it! We really did it! It's getting commercialized, seriously! And...
はい、ということでね、え、詳細はライブの後に発表されますのでね、ぜひチェックしてください！
Yes, so details will be announced after the live, so please check it out!
お願いします！
Please check it out!
ということでね、じゃあ猫はまだね、ちょっと歌うから、控室で待ってて。うん。じゃあね、ばいばい。はい、ばいばいばい。じゃあね。
Anyway, Neko, since I'm going to sing now, wait in the dressing room. See ya, bye-bye.
素直に去っていったよ。
It left so obediently.
ということで、じゃあね、え、後半戦、まだまだ続きますけれども、早速歌っていこうかなと思います！
So, the second half is still going to continue, but I'd like to go right into singing!
それでは聴いてください。みんなへの想いを込めて、2曲続けて歌います。
Now, please listen. Putting my feelings for everyone into it, I'll sing two songs back-to-back.
聴いてください、君色シグナル。
Please listen to "Kimiiro Signal".
放課後 二人で過ごした教室
After-school classroom where the two of us spent time
机の上 夢中で弾む君の声
Your voice bouncing excitedly on top of the desk
ぶっきらぼうな君のその態度が
Your blunt attitude
いつも私を意地悪にさせるの
Always makes me want to tease you
ひとりぼっちだと思う時もある
Sometimes I feel all alone
涙止められない日もある
Sometimes there are days when I can't stop my tears
本当の私を見つめてほしいの
I want you to look at the real me
きっと伝えると信じているよ
I believe that my feelings will reach you
君はいつだっていつだって変わらないから
You are always, always unchanging
私が何度も何度もシグナル送ってあげる
So I will send you signals over and over again
夢見たあの丘目指して
Aiming for the hill we dreamed of
くじけそうな時も 頑張れそうだよ 君がいるから
Even when I feel like giving up, I can do my best because you're here
ふたり 歩く いつもの帰り道
Walking together on our usual way home,
名前もない 気持ちが芽生え始めてる
nameless feelings are starting to sprout.
だけど 踏み出すための 勇気は
But the courage to take that step
少しだけ まだ遠くにある
is still a little bit far away.
何も 持っていなかった 私に
To me, who had nothing at all,
君が くれた 心の鍵は
the key to my heart that you gave me
胸の 奥で 眠ってたづぼみに
to the buds sleeping deep within my chest,
春の 日差しを 届けてくれる
you bring the spring sunlight.
君を いつだって いつだって 想っているから
Because I'm thinking of you always, always,
きっとね いつか いつか ちゃんと
I'm sure one day, one day, you'll understand properly—
わかってほしい 二人で描いた未来を
I want you to understand the future we drew together,
もっと近い距離で 見つめられるように 夢見ているから
dreaming that we can gaze upon it from an even closer distance.
みつめられるように 夢見ているから
dreaming that we can gaze upon it...
あの日ふれた 君のシグナル
That signal of yours I touched that day—
始まりの 扉がひらくよ
the door to the beginning opens.
君はいつだって いつだって 変わらないでね
Please never, ever change,
私に何回も何回も シグナル送ってほしい
send me signals over and over again.
輝く あの虹のように
Like that shining rainbow,
涙のあとも 奇跡に変えるよ
even tears will turn into miracles.
君はいつだって いつだって 変わらないから
Because you will never, ever change,
私が何回も何回も シグナル送ってあげる
I will send you signals over and over again.
夢見た あの丘目指して
Aiming for that hill we dreamed of,
くじけそうな時も 頑張れそうだよ
even when I feel like giving up, I can do my best
君がいるから
because you are here.
どっか 落ち着かないの 毎日
Every day is somehow restless,
退屈なんて ないけど
not that it's boring, though.
胸の痛み 苦しくて 泣きたい時もある
Chest pains hurt so much, and sometimes I just want to cry.
ささやかな 出来事さえも 特別だって 思うよ
Even the smallest occurrences feel so special.
ほらね 今も 君のことを 考えちゃうの
Look, even now, I find myself thinking about you.
好きと嫌い 交互に数えていく占い 1/2の確率
A fortune-telling counting "I like you," "I don't" alternately—a 50% chance,
それじゃ 踏み出せないね
so I can't take that step yet.
君と Fly 空見上げたら この気持ちだって言えるかな
If I fly with you and look up at the sky, could I tell you this is how I feel?
ひとつひとつ 言葉にしよう 笑って聞いてくれたなら
Let's put it into words, one by one. If you can smile and listen,
ああ この関係は 曖昧模倣っというのかな
ah, is this relationship vague and blurry?
徒然でも I wish I feel my sweet 大事にしなくちゃ
Even in idleness, I wish I feel my sweet, I must cherish it.
些細な出来事さえも 特別だって思うよ
Even the smallest events feel so special,
ほらね 今も君のこと 考えいちゃうの
Look, even now I find myself thinking of you.
好きと嫌い交互に数えていく占い 1/2の確率 それじゃ踏み出せないね
Alternating between likes and dislikes, a 50-50 chance—I can't take a step forward with that.
君と あぁ この関係は曖昧模糊っとしているのかな
You and I... Ah, is this relationship vague and hazy?
徒然でも I wish I feel my sweet 大事にしなくちゃ
Even leisurely, I wish I feel my sweet—I have to cherish it.
恋の仕方を解いても 正解なんかないでしょ?
Even if I figure out how to love, there's no right answer, is there?
君の気持ち ヒントさえ 見つからないよ
I can't even find a hint of your feelings.
「好き」の2文字何度頭の中唱える 秘密の言葉 想いはそれじゃ伝わらないね
How many times do I chant "I love you" in my head? Secret words—feelings won't get across like that.
君と Rise 空に描こう カラフルになったこの日々を
With you, Rise, let's paint the sky with these colorful days.
鮮やかさが 生まれてくよ 笑って 泣いて 胸の中
Vividness is born inside my chest, laughing and crying.
あぁ この感情が曖昧模糊っとしているのなら
Ah, if this emotion is vague and hazy,
徒然でも I wish I feel my sweet 大事にしたいな
even leisurely, I wish I feel my sweet—I want to cherish it.
すれ違う道も 離れてく距離も 向き合って心を開けたら
Even passing paths, even growing distance—if we face each other and open our hearts,
勇気を出して前に進めるさ 心にそっと触れるよ
we can muster courage to move forward and gently touch the heart.
君と Fly 空見上げたら 素直に好きって言えるかな
When I look up at the sky with you, Fly, can I honestly say "I love you"?
君のそばで 笑う未来 願っていたくて
I want to keep wishing for a future where I smile by your side.
あぁ この関係が曖昧模糊っとしているのかな
Ah, is this relationship vague and hazy?
徒然でも I wish I feel my sweet 大事にしなくちゃ
Even leisurely, I wish I feel my sweet—I have to cherish it.
すれ違う道も 離れてく距離も 向き合って心を開けたら
Even passing paths, even growing distance—if we face each other and open our hearts,
勇気を出して前に進めるさ 心にそっと触れるよ
we can muster courage to move forward and gently touch the heart.
君と Fly 空見上げたら 素直に好きって言えるかな
When I look up at the sky with you, Fly, can I honestly say "I love you"?
君のそばで 笑う未来 願っていたくて
I want to keep wishing for a future where I smile by your side.
心にそっと触れるよ 君と そう空見上げたら
I gently touch your heart. When I look up at the sky with you,
素直に好きって言えるかな 君のそばで 笑う未来 願っていたくて
can I honestly say "I love you"? I want to keep wishing for a future where I smile by your side.
きっと あぁ この関係が曖昧模糊っとしているのかな
Surely, ah, is this relationship vague and hazy?
徒然でも I wish I feel my sweet 大事にしなくちゃ
Even leisurely, I wish I feel my sweet—I have to cherish it.
きっと あぁ この関係が曖昧模糊っとしているのかな
Surely, ah, is this relationship vague and hazy?
徒然でも I wish I feel my sweet 大事にしなくちゃ
Even leisurely, I wish I feel my sweet—I have to cherish it.
いつか届くなら
If it reaches you someday...
すき
[Love]
ということで、今日短い時間だったけど、最後まで見てくれてありがとう！
And with that, today's stream was a bit short, but thank you for watching until the end!
いやね、3Dライブ本当に楽しかったです！
Man, this 3D live was really so much fun!
またね3Dライブやりたいと思ってるから、
I'm thinking of doing another 3D live,
よかったらまた歌みに来てくれると嬉しいなって思ってるよ！よろしくね！
so I'd be super happy if you'd come watch me sing again! See you!
ということで、今日はね、みんな本当に最後まで見てくださりありがとうございました！
So everyone, thank you truly so much for watching all the way to the end today!
このあとすぐ、なんと告知はねされてますけれども、
Right after this, there's an announcement, um—
えーメンバー限定の生放送で、えーみなとあくあ3D麺厳配信がありますので、よかったらねメンバー限定、えーメンバー登録もよろしくお願いします！よろしく！
there will be a member-exclusive 3D stream for Minato Aqua, so if you'd like, please consider joining as a member! Thanks!
ということで、最後とは言いましたけどあと1曲あります！あと1曲あります！
So with that, I said it was the last one, but there's one more song! There's one more song!
ということで、それではね、最後の曲はやっぱりあの曲で終わっていきたいと思います！
So then, we'll end with that song for the very last one!
ということで、最後の曲聞いてください！あくあいろぱれっと！
So please listen to the final song: "Akuiro Palette"!
何をしても不器用で
Clumsy at whatever I do,
何かとミスばっかり
making mistakes all the time.
ダメダメな私だって
Even though I'm a hopeless me,
できることがあるの
there are things I can do.
凹んで悲しくたって 笑顔にしてあげるんだ
Even if I'm down and sad, I'll make you smile.
ここにいるから 早く 私を見つけてね
I'm right here, so hurry up and find me!
LOVE YOU LOVE YOU I LOVE YOU
いつでも隣にいるし いつでも一緒に笑える
Always by your side, always able to laugh together.
私をたくさん知って たくさん好きって言って
Get to know me a lot, say you love me a lot.
ワガママで朝も苦手 ドジだしダメダメだけど それでも私のこと 見ていてね
Selfish, bad mornings, clumsy and hopeless—even so, keep watching over me.
何をしても不器用で
I'm so clumsy in everything I do,
何かとミスばっかだけど
making mistakes all the time.
それでも私のことを見ててね
Still, I want you to keep watching me.
描く夢の未来へ続く
May the path leading to the future of our dreams
道は君と歩けますように
be walked with you.
ねぇ もっと 好きになってもらいたいのもっと
Hey, I want you to love me even more!
頭の中は君ばっか
My head is full of you!
って言うかそっぽなんて向かせてよ
Don't you dare look away!
あぁもう! ヤキモキしちゃうわ
Ah geez! It makes me all anxious.
あぁ ずっとずっと好きがいいの
Ah, I want you to love me forever and ever.
心の奥もときめいちゃうくらいにこっち向いててよねぇ
Look this way enough to make my heart flutter deep inside, hey?
あぁもう離さないから絶対に!
Ah, I'm never letting go, absolutely!
(Love you, love you, I love you...)
君がいるから私 いつでもがんばるんだ
Because you're here, I can always do my best.
凹んで悲しくたって 君がいるから…
Even when I'm feeling down and sad, because you're here...
君がいるから 歩いて来れた
I was able to walk here because you were with me.
君がいなくちゃ 前も見れない
If you weren't here, I couldn't even see ahead.
嫌なこととか 辛いこととか あったって
Even if there were bad things or painful things,
君の力で ここまで笑ってこられたんだ
I managed to smile this far thanks to your strength.
今度はもっと私がぐっと引っ張って 連れて行くんだ
This time, I'll pull you in tighter and take you along!
君がいるから 私がいるの
Because you're here, I am here.
こんな私を 愛してくれる?
Will you love someone like me?
ねぇ もっと ねぇ もっと
Hey, more, hey, more,
まだ もっと 受け入れてよね!
Accept me even more!
ねぇ いい? さぁ声を出して!
Hey, is that okay? Now raise your voices!
ねぇ もっとねぇ もっと 好きになってもらいたいのに
Hey, more, hey, more, I want you to love me even more,
いつもそう私ばかりみたいにそっぽなんて向かせないわ
I won't let you look away like I'm the only one caring.
ねぇ ほら夢中にしちゃうわ あぁ ずっとずっと好きがいいの!
Hey, look, I'll make you obsessed! Ah, I want your love forever!
心も体も染まっちゃうくらいに こっち向いててよねぇ?
Look this way until my heart and soul are dyed in you, hey?
あぁ もう離さないから絶対に! 絶対ね 絶対よ 約束だよ
Ah, I'm never letting go, absolutely! Absolutely, it's a promise!
(Love you, love you, I love you...)
ねぇ もっと 好きになってもらいたいのもっともっと...
Hey, I want you to love me even more, more and more...
頭の中は君ばっか
My head is full of you!
って言うかそっぽなんて向かせてよ
Don't you dare look away!
あぁもう! ヤキモキしちゃうわ
Ah geez! It makes me all anxious.
あぁ ずっとずっと好きがいいの
Ah, I want you to love me forever and ever.
心の奥もときめいちゃうくらいにこっち向いててよねぇ
Look this way enough to make my heart flutter deep inside, hey?
あぁもう離さないから絶対に!
Ah, I'm never letting go, absolutely!
(Love you, love you, I love you...)
愛しちゃう もっと
I'll love you even more!
ありがとう!
Thank you so much!
皆さんどうもこんあくあー！湊あくあです！
Hello everyone, Konaqua! It's Minato Aqua!
ということで、あくあ色すーぱーみらくるどりーむ楽しんでいただけましたかー？
So, did you enjoy 'Aqua Iro Super Miracle Dream'?
当日の彼女はきっと緊張して胃が張り裂けそうなくらいな気持ちになっていると思うので、よかったら温かいコメントいっぱいしてくれたら嬉しいですって終わってんのかも！
I bet she was super nervous on the day, feeling like her stomach was gonna burst, so I'd be so happy if you left lots of warm comments! Wait, is it already over?!
ということで、ここからは告知タイム！重大告知もあるのでよかったら最後までお見逃しなく！
So from here on is announcement time! There's a major announcement too, so please don't miss the end!
それでは告知その1、行ってみましょう！てでーん！
Well then, let's go to announcement number one! Ta-da!
先ほどの3Dライブで出てきた、NEKO 3D化を記念して、NEKO BIGぬいぐるみがいよいよ発売されまーす！
To commemorate the NEKO 3D debut from earlier in the 3D live, the NEKO BIG plushie is finally going on sale!
全長約45センチ…や、約45ぐ、あ、あれ？や、約ってなんだろう……
Total length about 45 centimeters... W-wait, about 45 c-, wait, what? W-what does 'about' mean...
ということで、こちらは概要欄より、ご購入できますので、
So, you can purchase this from the description box below,
よかったら、購入チェック、チェック！
If you'd like, check out the purchase page, check, check!
一緒に遊ぶもよし、
It's great to play together,
お散歩に連れてくもよし、
great to take for walks,
寝るもよし、
great to sleep with,
殴るはちょっとやめてほしいけど、まあ
though I'd rather you didn't punch it, well...
抱きかかえるならよし。
hugging it is fine.
いっぱい使ってねー！
Use it lots!
告知その2！
Notice #2!
湊あくあ「Nyanyanyanyanyanyanya!」歌ってみた動画が届いたよ！
Minato Aqua's cover of "Nyanyanyanyanyanyanya!" is here!
このあとすぐ、マジ！
Coming right up, seriously!
ニャニャニャニャニャニャニャニャ…
Nyanyanyanyanyanyanya...
どんな動画になっているのかちょっとわからないと思うけどね、
You probably have no idea what kind of video it'll be, but
みんなよかったら観てね！このあとすぐだよ、絶対観てね！
everyone, please check it out! It's coming right up, definitely watch it!
絶対だよ！絶対だよ！絶対だからね！
Absolutely! Absolutely, okay?!
続いて、その3！
Next, Notice #3!
こちらもこのあとすぐ、えー
Also coming right up, um,
メンバー限定で初めての3D配信を行いたいと思います！
we'll be holding our very first member-limited 3D stream!
イェーイ！
Yay!
プリンセスね衣装で撮影会をしたりとか、
We'll be having a photo session in princess outfits,
あとまあ、感想をお話したりとか、ちょっと色々ねお話ししたり、えーと、
and chatting about our thoughts and various other things, um,
主と思ってるので、よかったらみんな、えー、メンバーシップ限定の放送を観に来てくれると嬉しいです！
so I'd be super happy if you all come watch the membership-exclusive broadcast!
「まだメンバーシップになってないよ」って方、
For those who aren't members yet,
今がチャンスです！
now's your chance!
よかったらメンバーシップの登録概要欄からできるので登録してってね！
If you'd like, you can sign up via the membership link in the description, so please subscribe!
みんなあくいろに染まれー！
Everybody, get dyed in Aqua color!
そしてそしてそして！10大告知行きます！
And, and, and! The 10th announcement is coming!
湊あくあ2021年8月8日デビュー3周年を記念したYouTube無料ライブ第2弾開催決定！イェーーイ！
Minato Aqua 2021 August 8th Debut 3rd Anniversary YouTube Free Live Part 2 Announced! Yay!
ということで、配信日などは、えー追ってお知らせするので、よかったらお待ちください！
So, the streaming date and details will be announced later, so please look forward to it!
ちょっとね、あくあ色すーぱーみらくるどりーむとはまた違った感じのライブにしたいなって考えてるから、楽しみにしててね！
I want to make this live concert feel a bit different from Aqua-iro Super Miracle Dream, so look forward to it!
それじゃあ本当の本当に最後までライブ観てくれてありがとう！
So, thank you so truly, truly much for watching the live stream all the way to the end!
以上、みなとあくあでした！
That's all from Minato Aqua!
バイバーイ！チュッ♥
Bye-bye! Muwah♥